-嘿  亲爱的  -嗨
-<i>Hey, honey.</i> -Hi.
-你拿的什么东西  -噢  是一幅画
-What you got there? -Oh, it's a wonderful painting
以一位明日之星所命名的
by an up-and-coming artist named,
正是鄙人  艾米·邓肯
huh, Amy Duncan.
说得好  嘿  你的第一节艺术课不是在今晚吗
That's right. Hey, you had your first art class tonight.
-学得怎么样啊  -不好说  还是你来告诉我吧
-How'd that go? -I don't know, you tell me.
震世之作
Ba-bam.
-画的什么东西  -再明显不过了
-What is it? -It's obvious.
噢  我知道了  是一个鸟巢里放了三个鸡蛋
Oh! Oh, I know. It's three eggs in a nest.
不对  不对  是一块烤白薯和三块黄油
No, wait. No, it's a baked potato with three pats of butter.
老爸  你看什么画都说那个
Dad, you see that in every painting.
噢  我觉着像雏鸡们在啃足球
Oh, I think it's baby chicks eating out of a football.
是柠檬  好不
Lemons, okay?
我画的是一碗柠檬
It's a bowl of lemons.
噢
Oh.
你们这帮人就不会欣赏艺术
You people have no appreciation for art.
噢  别生气啊  亲爱的  亲爱的
Oh, come on, honey. Honey.
-干吗  -别生气  古话说得好...
-What? -Come on, you know what they say...
如果生活给了你一碗柠檬...
If life gives you a bowl of lemons...
不是让你来画画的...
That's not very well painted...
而是让你来...做晚饭的
Then you should make... make dinner?
说得真好啊  老爸
Good save, dad.
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
■
翻译： Johnny-Z
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
■
校订： line
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第二季第七集
Good Luck Charlie  S02E07  Battle of the Bands
-嘿哥俩好啊  -你怎么来了
-Hey, guys. -What are you doing here?
你是来看我报名参加乐队比赛的吗
Did you come to see me sign up for the battle of the bands?
也许泰迪妹子是来看我的
Or maybe Teddy bear is here to see me.
是吗  难道比赛的主题就是
Okay, so the topic is
“泰迪现身商场的几大疯狂猜想”吗
"insane reasons why Teddy's at the mall."
算了  不扯了  我来这里也是为了参加比赛的
No no no, <i>i'm</i> here to sign up for battle of the bands.
-你有乐队吗  -有的
-You have a band? -Yes, I do.
我的朋友斯凯勒和我玩过一段时间音乐
My friend Skyler and I have been working on some music.
噢  不会吧...  是斯宾塞
Oh no... Spencer.
老兄  如果他也来参加  那我们就输定了
Man, if he's in this thing, we are toast.
说的没错  他在唱歌  跳舞  微笑上均天赋异禀
He's a complete package with the singing, the dancing and the sparkly smiling.
对不起  嘿  大家好吗
Excuse me. Hey, guys.
-嘿  -还不错
-Hey. -Mm-hmm.
看来现在你有...你有...你有乐队了
So you're... you're... you have a band now?
-没有  我准备一个人来表演  -是吗
-No, I'm gonna perform alone. -Huh.
但这是乐队比赛
Because this is battle of the bands
而且我很确定“乐队”这个词暗指是一个团体
and I'm pretty sure the word "band" implies group,
换而言之  要一人以上
I.E., more than one.
我是说  可能是我错了
I mean, I could be wrong,
但是我...不这么认为
but I don't... don't think so.
其实  我打电话问过  他们说我可以一个人表演...
Actually, I called and they said I could perform alone...
表演一些引人注目的节目
Something about drawing a bigger crowd.
我还不知道要表演什么
No, I don't know.
我还是回去排队吧  祝你们好运
I should get back in line, so good luck.
你发现了吗  他的牙并不是那么闪亮嘛
You know something? His teeth were <i>not</i> that sparkly.
我早就发现了
That's just what I was thinking.
老兄  我们会胜利的  因为我们是如此的给力
Dude, we're gonna win this thing because we are so insane.
-我们最给力了  碰下拳  -击下掌
-We're so insane. Fist bump. -Up top.
-碰  碰拳  击掌  -击掌  碰拳
-Fist... fist bump. Up top. -Up top. Fist bump.
好了  先停下  先停下
Okay, stop stop stop.
我们之前有做过啊  噢  等下
We've done this before. Oh, wait.
-嘿  -嘿
-Hey. -Hey.
手里拿的什么东西
What you got there?
全新的平板电脑  我的好朋友卢卡斯给我的
A brand-new mytab. My best friend Lucas gave it to me.
卢卡斯  没听过啊  你俩是好朋友多久了
Lucas? Never heard of him. How long have you guys been best friends?
自从今天三点他给我平板电脑后
Since 3:00 today when he gave me this mytab.
感觉像他在用金钱买你的友谊
Sounds like he's trying to buy your friendship.
是吗  那他得逞了
Well, it worked.
好了  这个礼物太昂贵了
Well, it's too expensive a gift.
-你还是快去还给他了吧  -什么  为什么
-You're gonna have to give it back. -What? Why?
你不能以物取人  以物会友
You shouldn't choose your friends because of the stuff they have.
如果某人只因为你有好东西而和你做朋友
Now how would you like it if people only liked you
你乐意吗
because you had nice things?
不如我先留着它  然后咱们再验证你的理论
Why don't I keep this and we'll test your theory?
盖比  如果你不还  我去还
Gabe, if you won't give it back, I will.
好吧
Fine.
好吧  老爸  我不再需要这玩意了
Fine, dad. I don't need this thing.
我还有其他好玩的
I have plenty of other great games to play with.
比如这个
Like this.
什么烂玩意
You <i>disgust</i> me.
好了
Okay.
-可以了吗  -什么可以了吗
-Shall we? -Shall we what?
排练歌曲
Rehearse the song.
-噢  想起来了  -好了
-Oh! Right. -Yeah.
我们还能做什么呢  我脑抽了
Duh! What else would we do? Airhead!
-可以了吗  -什么可以了吗
-Shall we? -Shall we what?
噢  一  二
Oh! One, two,
一  二  三
one, two, three.
我会静静等待
<i>I've been holding on</i>
直到看见你的脸庞
<i>Till I see your face</i>
来去更迭
<i>Been there and gone</i>
全是我的错
<i>And I own my mistakes</i>
时间静止...
<i>Time stands still...</i>
我爱的女孩要辣  辣  辣
<i>I like girls who are hot hot hot</i>
和不辣的女孩说拜  拜  拜...
<i>Better than girls who are not not not...</i>
停一下
Excuse me!
你们俩  我们正准备排练呢
Guys, we are trying to rehearse!
我们也是
So are <i>we.</i>
-嗨  -嗨
-Hi. -Hi.
-我是...我是PJ  -我是斯凯勒
-I'm... I'm P.J. -I'm Skyler.
-我是埃米特  -也许你们俩应该去别处排练去
-I'm Emmett. -Maybe you guys should go rehearse somewhere else?
-或者咱们去别处  -亲爱的斯凯勒  借一步说话
-Or we could. -Skyler dear, a word.
听着  咱们先来的
See, we were here first,
如果非要有人离开的话  那就是他们
so if anyone's leaving, it's them.
现在你要全力支持我  明白吗
Now you have to back me up on this, okay?
-明白  -好的
-Got it. -Okay.
-我们先来的  -没错
-We were here first. -Yeah!
-我们是不会走的  -没错
-And we're not leaving. -Yeah!
-我们也不走  -没错
-We're not leaving either. -Yeah!
好了  你需要呼应的是我
Okay, only after I say stuff.
明白
Got it.
斯凯勒  咱们走  咱们去把比赛赢下来
Skyler, let's go. We have a contest to win.
没错  我们也是
Yeah, well, so do we.
我想知道你的梦想
I wanna know what you dream
我想知道你的愿望...
I wanna know</i> <i>what you wish...
我爱的女孩要辣  辣  辣
I like girls who are hot hot hot
和不辣的女孩说拜  拜  拜
Better than girls who are not not not
我想知道你是否关心
I wanna know if you care!
三  二  一
Three, two, one.
您好  达布尼太太
Hello, Mrs. Dabney.
快瞧瞧咱俩  查莉  像不像艺术界的双娇啊
Look at us, Charlie. Aren't we a couple of artists?
那是当然的了  过来
We are. Come here.
噢  好闺女
Oh, that's my girl.
我画的这是什么
Now what is this?
-一棵树  -没错  就是一棵树
-A tree. -A tree. It is a tree.
好了  你在画什么呢
Okay. Now what are you painting?
-树  -树吗
-Tree. -A tree?
不对  宝贝  妈妈我画的才是树
No, honey, mommy's is a tree,
你画的是一堆曲线  是吧
yours is just a bunch of squiggly lines, okay?
好了  你知道吗
Okay, but you know what?
我们还是会把它挂在墙上的
We're gonna put it on the wall anyway.
就放在这
Put it right there.
这是树
A tree.
谁信啊
I don't think so.
鲍伯  你能帮查莉收拾一下吗
Bob honey, could you clean up Charlie?
那是我的天职
<i>I live for it.</i>
瓦珥  我的观音菩萨  怎么是你
Val! Oh my goodness. What a surprise.
-快请进  -我前来是想和你谈谈艺术课的事情
-Please please, come in. -I came to talk to you about art class.
-好的  -从我身上的感觉不难看出
-Yeah. -As you can probably tell by my aura...
...我带来了坏消息
...I bring bad news.
-什么  什么坏消息  -过来
-What? What is it? -Come.
艾米  我教授艺术课已多年了
Amy, I have been teaching art for many years,
我一直深信每个人
and I've always believed that everybody
都是有艺术才能的  不论他隐藏的有多深
has artistic ability, no matter how deeply buried.
直到我遇见了你
And then I met you.
什么  你认为我没有天赋吗
What? You don't think I have talent?
噢  这可是你说的  不是我说的
Oh! Your words, not mine.
如果非要让我说
Although if I were to use words,
我也会这么说的
I'd choose those.
这个  呃  能再给我一次机会吗
Well, uh, give me another chance.
那是什么  天啊
What is that?! Oh!
简直是神作啊
It's glorious!
激情迸发  充满活力
What passion! What vibrancy!
噢  艾米  你这种快乐式作画
Oh, Amy, you paint with a joy
看起来天真烂漫
that's almost childlike.
-这个嘛  其实...  -真是绝了
-Well, actually... -It's genius!
谢谢
Thank you.
这就是你以后要发展的方向...
This is what you should be focusing on...
抽象派
Abstract work.
谢谢
Thank you.
我要表现的是...“树”
I call it... "Tree."
-嗨  -嗨
-Hi. -Hi.
-泰迪在吗  -其实  她还没回来呢
-Is Teddy here? -Actually, she's not home yet.
-请进吧  -谢谢
-Come on in. -Thanks.
噢  我很喜欢你们昨天的歌
Oh, I liked your song yesterday.
噢  噢  谢谢
Oh! Oh, thanks.
是啊  我也喜欢
Yeah, I like it too.
不是  我是说我也喜欢你们的歌
No, I mean I liked your song too.
其实  我...我没怎么听到
Well, I... I didn't really hear it,
但我喜欢...你的秀发
but I like... your hair.
谢谢  我也喜欢你的秀发
Thanks. I like your hair too.
能有一头像你这么好的秀发的男友
It must be nice for your girlfriend
你的女友一定很幸运
to have a boyfriend who has such great hair.
我没有女友
I don't have a girlfriend.
-噢  太悲剧了  -是啊
-Oh, that's too bad. -Yeah.
但是  呃...
But, umm...
如果你告诉你的男友
If you want to tell your boyfriend
我没有女友的话
that I don't have a girlfriend,
我也不会介意的
I'm cool with that.
我没有男友
I don't have a boyfriend.
惨剧啊
Bummer.
-抱歉我迟到了  -噢  没事的
-Sorry I'm late. -Oh, no problem.
-PJ陪着我呢  -同样对那抱歉
-P.J.'s been keeping me company. - Sorry about that too.
好了  来吧  排练去
All right. Come on, let's rehearse.
嘿  别打扰我们
Hey, don't bother us.
没错  别打扰我们
Yeah, don't bother us.
老爸  这是盖比的爸爸
Dad, this is Gabe's dad.
-嘿  我叫鲍伯  -幸会  我叫布鲁斯
-Hey, I'm Bob. -Nice to meet you. I'm Bruce.
哇  这真是...
Wow, this is...
你这房间还真不赖
This is quite the room you've got here.
-是啊  -噢  天啊
-Yeah. -Oh man!
-星球中队  -没错  没错  我这里有一些
-Star squadron? -Yeah yeah, I've got kind of a thing
-老式的电子游戏  -哇
-for old arcade games. - Wow.
知道吗  如果再来一大盘玉米饼和一杯根汁汽水
You know, if I had a trayful of tacos and a root beer,
那就完全像重返高中岁月了
this would be like High School all over again.
艾伯特  能弄上来点
Albert, can I get
一大盘玉米饼和一杯根汁汽水吗  谢了
a trayful of tacos and some root beer? Thanks.
你和我开玩笑呢吧
You're kidding, right?
我从来不开玉米饼的玩笑  鲍伯
I never kid about tacos, Bob.
我刚才正想看比赛呢
I was just about to watch the game.
想一起看吗
You wanna join me?
噢  真是太爽了
Oh, this is awesome!
噢  噢  噢  鲍伯  你找我什么事来着
Oh oh oh, Bob, what was it you wanted to talk to me about?
噢  我是想...
Oh, I just wanted to...
噢  玉米船来了
Oh! Here comes the taco boat.
呃  我...
Umm, I...
我...我只是想告诉你我有多开心
I-I... I just wanted to say how happy I am
盖比和卢卡斯  你和我
that Gabe and Lucas and you and me
-都成了好朋友  -噢
-are best friends. -Oh.
盖比  经过我再三考虑
Gabe, I thought it over,
-还给你  -你...你让我留着了
-and here. -Y-you're gonna let me keep it?
你怎么改变主意了
Why'd you change your mind?
因为我不是一个蛮不讲理的人
Because I'm not an unreasonable man.
事实上  我相当通情达理
In fact, I'm so not unreasonable,
我也给自己弄了一个
I accepted one myself.
不不...我不是抱怨
Not-not... not that I'm complaining,
只是你向我传达了一种错综复杂的信息
but you're sending me some mixed messages here.
我更愿意称之为柔性信息
I like to think of them as <i>flexible</i> messages.
你去他们家了  是不是
You saw the den, didn't you?
我吃了两大盘玉米饼
I had two trays of tacos.
这周日还会有更多的
And we're gonna have more this Sunday,
因为我们又约好了一起看比赛
because we got invited over to watch the football game.
欢迎投靠黑暗势力
Welcome to the dark side.
我们一直在等待着你
We've been expecting you.
噢  斯宾塞  你看见斯凯勒了吗
Oh, Spencer, have you seen Skyler anywhere?
没有  不过我快到胜利的终点了...
Nope, but it's almost time for me to win...
我是说去乐队比赛
I mean compete in battle of the bands,
-那么我先走了  -好的
-so I should get going. -Right.
多谢帮助
Thanks for your help.
你个混蛋
Clump nugget.
噢  斯凯勒  你在这呢  我正在找你呢
Oh, Skyler, there you are. I've been looking all over for you.
噢  我在照大头贴呢
Oh, I was in the photo booth.
是啊  是啊  我现在知道了
Yup yup, I see that now.
好了  咱们该走了  是时间该...
Come on, we have to get going. It's almost time for us to go...
其实  我不想参加比赛了
Actually, I don't want to do the contest anymore.
-什么  为什么  -这个  因为...
-What? Why not? -Well, because...
我不想和我的男朋友对抗竞争
I don't want to compete against my boyfriend.
男朋友  谁是你的男朋友
Boyfriend? Who's your boyfriend?
不会吧  不会吧  不会吧
No. No. No!
会的  会的  会的
Yes yes yes.
这么说你俩恋爱的
And so you guys are a couple?
没错  PJ是我男友
That's right, P.J.'S my dude.
-斯凯勒是我的女友  -嗯
-And Skyler's my lady. -Mm-hmm.
我要快吐了
And Teddy's gonna hurl.
这就是你为什么不参加比赛了
Wha... so that's why you don't want to do battle of the bands?
-因为你们恋爱了  -没错
-Because you're a couple? -That's right,
因为这些竞争对抗不利于我俩关系的发展
'cause competing against each other would not be good for our relationship.
-那咱俩的歌怎么办  -你可以独唱
-But what about our song? -You can sing it.
-但那是合唱曲目  -那又怎样
-But it's a duet. -So?
所以我不能没有你来进行合唱
So I can't "du-et" without you.
-嘿  大家  怎么了  -嘿  老兄
-Hey, guys. What's going on? -Hey, man.
我来告诉你怎么了  PJ和斯凯勒谈恋爱了
I'll tell you what's going on. P.J. And Skyler are a couple
现在他们不想比赛了
and now they don't want to do battle of the bands.
什么  难道就这么前功尽弃了
What? After all our hard work?
我还邀请了我老妈来看
I even asked my mom to come.
那就对不起让她失望了
Well, sorry to disappoint her.
噢  没事的  反正她拒绝了我的邀请
Oh no, it's okay. She said no.
来啊  来啊  查莉
Come on. Come on, Charlie.
-再给妈妈画幅画  -我累了
-One painting for mama? -I tired.
好吧  不如这样  查莉  再画一小下
Okay, come on, Charlie. Just one little painting
我就让你回去睡觉
and you can go back to sleep.
嘿  查莉怎么起来了
Hey, what's Charlie doing up?
我刚把她安顿好去睡觉
I just put her down for a nap.
噢  我猜她又恢复精神了
Oh, well, I guess she just got her second wind.
我累了
I tired.
我不知道她说的是什么
Don't know where that came from.
好了
All right.
到底怎么回事  你怎么比平常还疯狂了
What's going on? Why are you acting crazier than usual?
我的艺术课老师跑来告诉我  我很烂
My art teacher came over to tell me that I stink.
好的  目前为止我还听得懂
Okay, I'm with you so far.
然后她看了一眼查莉画的东西
Then she took one look at Charlie's painting
就被迷住了  所以...
and loved it, so...
你这不是霸占功劳吗
You took the credit for it.
那个  我生的查莉
Well, I made Charlie,
要这么说来  那就是我画的画
so in a way, I made that painting.
亲爱的  要按这个逻辑  我也参与了这幅画的制作
Honey, by that logic, I made that painting too.
是吗  难道那幅画是在你的肚子里
Really? You carried that painting around
装了九个月吗
inside of you for nine months?
什么
What?
鲍伯  我只是想把我做的每件事都做到尽善尽美
Bob, I just wanna be the best at what I do.
亲爱的  你有很多事情
Honey, you are the best
都做到尽善尽美了
at a lot of things.
你是位很好的护士
You're the best nurse.
你是位很好的母亲  你也是位很好的妻子
You're the best mommy. You're the best wife.
-不要停下  -好了
-Go on. -Okay.
不如这样...  你把查莉放回床上
I'll tell you what... why don't we put Charlie to bed
然后咱俩互相抱抱
and then you and I can cuddle?
因为你在那方面也很出色
Because you are also the best at that.
我累了
I tired.
我无法再四处追寻你
<i>I can't keep chasing you around</i>
这些追寻只会让我深感绝望
<i>All of this running is just bringing me down</i>
让我绝望
<i>It's got me down</i>
每次当我注视你
<i>Every time I look at you</i>
天使都在歌唱
<i>The angels sing</i>
但愿你也可以听到
<i>I hope you hear them too</i>
噢  但愿你也可以听到
<i>Oh, I hope you hear them too</i>
让我感觉魂牵梦绕
<i>Got me feeling hypnotized</i>
女孩 让我感觉还活着...
<i>Girl, it makes me feel alive...</i>
好了  你是在看...
Well, would you look at that...
我们的前男友是如何勇夺桂冠的吗
Our ex-boyfriend's gonna win this thing.
我才不关心呢  我有新男友了
I don't care. I have a new boyfriend.
你也可以有
You could too.
这...这太让我气愤了
It just... it makes me so mad.
就因为你们俩谈恋爱  使得我们无法比赛了
Because you two became an annoying couple, we can't compete.
-等一下  -噢  我了解那个表情
-Wait a minute. -Ooh, I know that look.
她要有办法了  我就从没有过那种表情
She's getting an idea. I never get that look.
我也是
Me neither!
噢
Aww.
噢  天啊  我是相当期待今晚啊
Oh! Man, I'm looking forward to tonight.
-噢  是啊  应该是场精彩的比赛  -绝对精彩
-Oh yeah, it should be a good game. -Game-shmame.
据说艾伯特准备了新鲜的鳄梨酱
There's a rumor Albert made fresh guacamole.
这不是据说...是真的
The rumor... is true.
老爸  我要回家
Dad, I wanna go home.
什么  比赛都快开始了
What? It's almost kick-off.
我们在玩“女巫大战术士三”时
We were playing "witches versus warlocks 3"
-他居然说我作弊  -因为你就是作弊了
-and he said I cheated. -Because you did cheat.
我没有作弊  是我打赢你了
I did not cheat. I <i>beat</i> you.
-因为你作弊了  -别吵了  小伙子们
-Because you cheated! -Take it easy, guys.
-但是  爸爸  -卢卡斯
-But, dad! -Lucas.
跟我来
Come with me.
老爸  我没有作弊
Dad, I didn't cheat.
-真的  -真的
-Really? -Yes!
听着  我以前做过弊
Look, I've cheated before.
对此我很在行  如果我真的作弊了
I'm good at it. If I had really cheated,
他是不会发觉的
he would <i>not</i> have known about it.
这简直就是对我作弊能力的羞辱
This is an insult to my cheating
-我绝不会容忍这事的  -好了  好了
-and I will not stand for it! -Okay okay, all right.
我觉着我明白了
I think I understand.
你就不能假装承认你作弊了吗
Couldn't you just say you cheated?
你要我去为那些我没有做错的事情去道歉
You want me to apologize for something I didn't do?
艾伯特可是做了新鲜的鳄梨酱啊
Albert made fresh guacamole.
鲍伯  我儿子那是相当的不爽啊
Bob, my boy's pretty upset.
不如赶紧让你儿子去向卢卡斯道歉吧
Now why don't you just have Gabe apologize to Lucas,
不要毁了咱俩看比赛
so that you and I can enjoy the game?
没门  我相信我儿子  布鲁斯
No, I believe my boy, Bruce.
如果他说他没有作弊  那他就是没有作弊
If he said he didn't cheat, he didn't cheat.
-谢了  老爸  -是啊  好吧
-Thanks dad. -Yeah, well,
我想咱们该走了
I think we should get going.
知道吗  鲍伯  我很敬佩你是如此相信你儿子
You know, Bob, I admire that you stood up for your son.
-这么说来你想让我们留下了  -没有
-So you want us to stay? -No.
平板电脑不还了
Keeping the mytab.
好了  耶
All right! Yeah!
好了  下一个出场的是PJ感应乐队
Okay, now our next band is P.J. And the vibe,
和泰迪与斯凯勒
plus Teddy and Skyler.
呃  这首歌是关于新的爱情
Um, this is a song about new love
还有是如何找到真爱的
and how people find each other,
甚至不惜惹怒某人的老妹
even though it might annoy someone's sister.
我一直在找寻
<i>I've been looking for</i>
可以真正看清我的人
<i>Someone who can see</i>
我到底是谁
<i>Who I really am</i>
我的内心世界到底如何
<i>What's inside of me</i>
我爱的女孩要辣  辣  辣
<i>I like girls who are hot hot hot</i>
和不爱的女孩说拜  拜  拜
<i>Better than girls who are not not not!</i>
你不是我所见过的
<i>You're not the smartest guy</i>
最聪明的男生
<i>That I ever met</i>
但你真的很可爱
<i>But you're really cute</i>
我心驰神往
<i>And I'm desperate</i>
你要的男孩就是我  我  我
<i>I'm the guy that you got got got</i>
多谢对我刮目相看  看  看
<i>Thanks for overlooking a lot lot lot</i>
-我心驰神往  -我很帅  帅  帅
<i>-I'm desperate -And I'm hot hot hot</i>
-我心驰神往  -多谢给我一次机会  会  会
<i>-I'm desperate -Thanks for the shot shot shot</i>
-我心驰神往  -我很帅  帅  帅
<i>-I'm desperate -And I'm hot hot hot</i>
-多谢给我一次机会  会  会  -为你
<i>-Thanks for the shot shot shot -For you.</i>
噢  完全超出我的想象  非常好
oh! I did not expect that. All right!
把掌声送给PJ...泰勒  斯凯勒什么的
Give it up for P.J., Tyler, Skyler and whatever.
噢
Oh.
好了  评委给出了他们最后的决定
Okay, the judges have made their final decision.
第三名将获得价值一百元的丛林滑板礼券
In third place, the winner of the $100 gift certificate
获奖者是...
to skateboard jungle is...
吉他老头儿
The guitar geezers.
好样的  伙计们
Great job, fellas.
现在请出我们的两队参赛选手
And now let's bring out our two finalists.
斯宾塞·沃尔什  请上来
Spencer Walsh, come on up.
PJ还有你们那一帮  也上来
P.J. And them, y'all come on over here too.
来吧
Come on.
好了  冠军将获得
<i>All right,</i> <i>and the winner</i>
价值五百元的购物礼卷  获奖的是
of the $500 shopping spree is
泰迪与斯凯勒和PJ感应乐队
Teddy and Skyler plus P.J. And the vibe!
-恭喜  -谢谢
-Congratulations. -Thanks.
祝你们乐极生悲
Clump nugget.
-泰迪  你刚刚抱了我  -是啊  我知道
-Teddy, you just hugged me. -Yeah, I know.
我真的好开心
I'm just really happy.
噢  是吗  我倒是没什么感觉
Oh no, I'm cool with that.
嘿  查莉  你还记得我的前男友斯宾塞吧
Hey, Charlie, you remember my old boyfriend Spencer, right?
在乐队比赛中完全被我们秒杀掉
Totally stomped him in battle of the bands!
感觉爽不  当然了
Did it feel good? Yes.
没错  女士  爽歪歪了
Yes, ma'am, it did.
-还感觉...  -嘿  你能安静点吗
-It also felt... -Hey, do you want to keep it down over there?
你们干嘛呢
<i>What are you doing?</i>
我们在我们自己的舒适的热浴缸里
We are watching the big game
看比赛呢
in the comfort of our own hot tub,
完全比在布鲁斯和卢卡斯家
which is every bit as good as being over
-好一万倍  -哪有  一点也不好
-at Bruce and Lucas's house. -No, it's not.
我知道不怎么好
I know it's not.
有时候我认为拍下这种镜头
Sometimes I wonder if recording moments like this
会给你留下阴影的
is just gonna scar you.
我猜以后就会知道了
I guess we'll find out later.
好运喽  查莉
Good luck, Charlie.
噢  这才叫做生活
Oh, this is the life.
没错  无与伦比啊
Yup, nothing like it.
我们甚至有我们自己的佣人
We even have our own Butler.
说到这个
Speaking of which.
快点  杯子可不会自己填满的
Let's go! These glasses aren't gonna fill themselves!
我累了
I tired.
知道了 知道了  再来点啤酒根汁汽水
Yeah yeah, okay. More root beer.
称心满意的服务真是难找
Good help is so hard to find.
哪来的气泡  我没看见你打开它们啊
Bubbles? I didn't see you turn them on.
我没有  三大盘玉米饼下肚
I didn't. Three trays of tacos,
你也会有自己的气泡的
you gonna get some bubbles.